export const QUIZ_CONTENT = {
  title: "10までの数",
  subject: "purple",
  category: "basic",
  data: [
    {
      id: "01",
      question: "one",
      answers: ["1", "0", "2", "10"],
      correct: "1",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「one」は「1」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "02",
      question: "two",
      answers: ["1", "3", "2", "7"],
      correct: "2",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「two」は「2」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "03",
      question: "three",
      answers: ["8", "3", "4", "6"],
      correct: "3",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「three」は「3」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "04",
      question: "nine",
      answers: ["5", "9", "6", "7"],
      correct: "9",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「nine」は「9」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "05",
      question: "eight",
      answers: ["8", "7", "6", "5"],
      correct: "8",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「eight」は「8」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "06",
      question: "six",
      answers: ["9", "2", "3", "6"],
      correct: "6",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「six」は「6」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "07",
      question: "ten",
      answers: ["10", "1", "5", "8"],
      correct: "10",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「ten」は「10」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "08",
      question: "four",
      answers: ["4", "2", "3", "5"],
      correct: "4",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「four」は「4」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "09",
      question: "seven",
      answers: ["7", "8", "9", "6"],
      correct: "7",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「seven」は「7」だよ。",
      image: ""
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "five",
      answers: ["5", "4", "3", "2"],
      correct: "5",
      hint: "",
      explanation: "「five」は「5」だよ。",
      image: ""
    }
  ]
}

export default {
  english01: QUIZ_CONTENT,
};